https://www.exceller.com/privacy-policy/

Exceller Privacy Policy
Exceller Software Corporation (“Exceller”) recognizes that Users (“Your”) personal information, such as name, address, e-mail address, phone, and credit card information is confidential. Our website and our products, “the Software” is on a secure web server, and our e-commerce software tools including, gateway and shopping cart, is certified to be secure and PCI compliant.
Exceller’s policy is not to share your personal information with third parties, without your consent. However, Exceller may use your personal information to inform you of Upgrades, and complimentary new products, provided you are over 13 years of age.
Exceller has no intention of obtaining personal information from minors (under 13 years of age). If Exceller can identify a User as a minor, their personal information will not be used for any marketing, or promotion of any other complimentary products, and their personal information will not be shared with any third parties for any reason whatsoever.
Special Notice to Parents
Exceller encourages you to ask your children, to seek your permission, before providing personal information about themselves or their family, for any reason, including any software purchases or downloads over the Internet.
Special Notice to Children (under 13 years of age)
Exceller encourages you to seek your parents’ permission prior to giving out any personal information of yours or your parents’ over the Internet, for any reason whatsoever, including any software purchases or downloads.
